https://www.blackfives.org/privacy/

Home
Mission
Overview
Welcome!
New York All Stars
New York Renaissance (‘Rens’)
Hudson “Huddy” Oliver
Cumberland “Cum” Posey, Jr.
Overview
Welcome!
New York All Stars
New York Renaissance (‘Rens’)
Hudson “Huddy” Oliver
Cumberland “Cum” Posey, Jr.
Privacy Policy
The Black Fives Foundation (“Black Fives” or “We”) takes your privacy seriously. We will never sell, rent or in any other way make your personal information available to an unaffiliated third party for their marketing purposes.
Please take a moment to read this Privacy Policy for a better understanding of the measures We take to protect you.
We collect two kinds of information from visitors to our website: aggregate information that is not personally identifiable (“Non-Personal Information”), and, by permission only, personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”).
Non Personal Information includes tracking the IP address of each visitor for the purpose of tabulating statistics about the pages visited, where they are visiting from, how they found our website (e.g., via Google), how they navigate the website, and/or the average length of time they spent on the site.
When visitors join our email list and/or make a donation, they may elect to supply personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) such as their name, email address, and/or mailing address.
Our website content may include links to other websites, such as those of our affiliates or partners, however, these other websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review each individual web site’s privacy policy when visiting them. While we attempt to carefully screen the websites and/or online content to which we link through BlackFives.org, the Black Fives Foundation assumes no responsibility for the privacy policies on any of the websites outside of its direct control.
1. How We Use the Information We Collect
To Analyze and Review:  We analyze and review aggregate, statistical information in order to continually refine and enhance the Black Fives website, its content, and the quality of your experience for each visit, for example by identifying trends to see what content is of most interest.
To Evaluate: We evaluate how our visitors use and navigate our website and its pages on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors to each web page, and the length of their visits.
To Communicate: We communicate with you via email regarding new features, news, events, and/or services; Once you have joined our email list, you may leave the list (“unsubscribe or “opt-out”) at any time.
To Respond: We may use collected information to respond to your questions, requests, or comments.
To Ask Questions: We may use information we collect in order to conduct polls, surveys and consumer testing.
To Confirm and Process: We will confirm and process donation transactions and/or contact you with follow up questions and/or communications about your donation.
To Comply: It may be necessary for us to comply with third-party organizations such as law enforcement when required or permitted by law, regulation, legal process or enforceable government request.
2. How is the Information Collected?
By Joining Our eMail List: When you elect to join our email list we ask you to supply personal information such as your name and email address, as well as your mailing address, zip or postal code, state or province, and country. Only the email address is mandatory, otherwise we will not be able to contact you, which would defeat the purpose of your joining. In addition, some form of name (it could be your nickname) is required.
When You Make an Online Donation: When you make an online donation (thank you for your generosity), our e-commerce supplier, PayPal, and/or its affiliates, are responsible for handling your payment authorization. They collect your financial data including contact name, credit card information, and/or other required information in order to complete the transaction on their secure site. This information is strictly confidential and their privacy policy is available online at their website. BlackFives.org does not retain copies of this information on its own servers.
When You Visit Our Website: We automatically collect Non-Personal Information on all visitors to our website. This includes collecting the IP address for each visitor in order to accumulate and track aggregate website usage statistics. We do not monitor usage on an individual basis. To the extent that IP addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, We also treat these identifiers as Personal Information for purposes of this Privacy Policy. Also, to the extent that Non-Personal Information is combined with Personal Information about you, We treat the combined information as Personal Information for purposes of this Privacy Policy.
Surveys: We may conduct occasional online surveys to improve our service or to seek the opinions of our visitors. These surveys are entirely voluntary and anyone presented with such a survey may decline to participate.
Tell A Friend: You may choose to recommend the BlackFives.org website to a friend. Once you provide their email address We will add this information to our database and send them emails with announcements, news, or other information inviting them to visit BlackFives.org. They may “opt out” of these announcements at any time.
Cookies: A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive that is necessary to identify and dynamically build customized pages. The Black Fives Foundation does not place cookies on the hard drives of its visitors at this time, but reserves the right to do so, at which time a link, pop up window, or other notification will appear in your web browser to advise you of this change in our practice.
Children: The BlackFives.org website is not directed at individuals under thirteen years of age, and in keeping with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, The Black Fives Foundation will not knowingly collect any Personal Information from such individuals without first seeking prior verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that a user of our website is under the age of 13 and has provided their email address or other Personal Information without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove that child’s Personal Information from our files.
3. How to Opt-Out?
You may be required to provide Personal Information if you wish to use certain features on BlackFives.org, however, you may choose to “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” of receiving emails, invitations, or promotional offers from The Black Fives Foundation at any time after you join our email list. You may also opt out of receiving any communication from us by contacting us directly.
4. The Black Fives Foundation Rights and Responsibilities
Security: The Personal Information that We collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We use and will use commercially reasonable efforts to maintain proper safeguards for the protection and security of these servers.
Policy Modifications: The Black Fives Foundation may edit this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that these changes will not use the Personal Information you submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy without your prior consent.
Rights: The Black Fives Foundation reserves the right to disclose and use Personal Information in special circumstances such as where it is necessary to enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use. We may also disclose or use Personal Information when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so.
Comments and Questions: If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us directly.
5. Rights of European Union Residents
For residents of the European Union, the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) requires that We take particular measures to protect the personal data of European residents. If there is any conflict between this policy and the GDPR, the GDPR principles shall govern with respect to residents of the European Union.
Under the GDPR, you have the right to request a copy of your personal data stored at The Black Fives Foundation (Article 15 GDPR). You also have the right to request corrections (Article 16 GDPR), deletion (Article 17 GDPR) or restriction (Article 18 GDPR) of your personal data stored with the Black Fives Foundation.
You may send your requests for access, correction, deletion or restriction to our attention: inspiration [at] blackfives.org.
If a European resident is dissatisfied with the handling of your personal data by the Black Fives Foundation, you have the right to object to the processing of your personal data at any time (Article 21 GDPR). You may send your concerns or objections about the processing of your personal data to inspiration [at] blackfives.org. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
6. Non-European Residents
Please be aware that your Personal Information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that we may process and store all information in the United States. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By using our Service, you agree that the collection, use, transfer and disclosure of your Personal Information and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 14, 2018.
